omorashi.org 2019-12-14

# Privacy Policy - OmoOrg

##  Policy summary 

##  Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services: 

  *     * ###  Analytics 

      * ###  Analytics collected directly and Google Analytics 

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage data 

    * ###  Contacting the User 

      * ###  Contact form and Mailing List or Newsletter 

Personal Data: email address 

    * ###  Content commenting 

      * ###  Comment system managed directly 

Personal Data: Cookies, Usage data, username, and website 

    * ###  Displaying content from external platforms 

      * ###  Google Fonts 

Personal Data: Usage data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service 

      * ###  Gravatar 

Personal Data: email address and Usage data 

      * ###  SoundCloud widget and YouTube video widget without cookies 

Personal Data: Usage data 

      * ###  Spotify widget, Vimeo video, and Vine widget 

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage data 

    * ###  Hosting and backend infrastructure 

      * ###  Amazon Web Services 

Personal Data: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service 

    * ###  Infrastructure monitoring 

      * ###  New Relic 

Personal Data: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service 

    * ###  Social features 

      * ###  Public profile 

Personal Data: country, date of birth, gender, picture and username 

    * ###  SPAM protection 

      * ###  Google reCAPTCHA 

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage data 

      * 

##  Further information about Personal Data 

  *     * ###  Selling goods and services online 

The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell products, including payment and possible delivery.

The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by this Application depends on the payment system used. 

    * ###  The Service is not directed to minors under the age of 18 

Users declare themselves to be an adult according to their applicable legislation. Under no circumstance persons under the age of 18 may use this Application. 

##  Contact information 

  *     * ###  Data owner 

Kirito (OmoOrg), admin@omorashi.org 

##  Full policy 

##  Data Controller and Owner 

Kirito (OmoOrg),  
admin@omorashi.org 

##  Types of Data collected 

Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are Cookies, Usage data, email address, username, website, gender, date of birth, country and picture. 

Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.  
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application.  
Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by this Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services. 

Users are responsible for any Personal Data of third parties obtained, published or shared through this Application and confirm that they have the third party's consent to provide the Data to the Owner. 

##  Mode and place of processing the Data 

###  Methods of processing 

The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in a proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/, or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Data Controller, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. 

###  Place 

The Data is processed at the Data Controller's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact the Data Controller. 

###  Retention time 

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request that the Data Controller suspend or remove the data. 

##  The use of the collected Data 

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, Contacting the User, Content commenting, Displaying content from external platforms, Hosting and backend infrastructure, Infrastructure monitoring, Social features and SPAM protection. 

The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document. 

##  Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data 

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services: 

  * ###  Analytics 

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior. 

####  Analytics collected directly (This Application) 

This Application uses an internal analytics system that does not involve third parties. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. 

####  Google Analytics (Google Inc.) 

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

  * ###  Contacting the User 

####  Contact form (This Application) 

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes this Application to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header. 

Personal Data collected: email address. 

####  Mailing List or Newsletter (This Application) 

By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning this Application. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to this Application or after making a purchase. 

Personal Data collected: email address. 

  * ###  Content commenting 

Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of this Application.  
Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.  
If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service. 

####  Comment system managed directly (This Application) 

This Application has its own internal content comment system. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies, Usage data, username, and website. 

  * ###  Displaying content from external platforms 

This type of services allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Application and interact with them.  
This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it. 

####  Google Fonts (Google Inc.) 

Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate the content of this kind on its pages. 

Personal Data collected: Usage data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.it/intl/policies/privacy/)

####  Gravatar (Automattic Inc.) 

Gravatar is an image visualization service provided by Automattic Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate the content of this kind on its pages.  
Please note that if Gravatar images are used for comment forms, the commenter's email address or parts of it may be sent to Gravatar - even if the commenter has not signed up for that service. 

Personal Data collected: email address and Usage data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/)

####  SoundCloud widget (SoundCloud Limited) 

Soundcloud is an audio content delivery service provided by SoundCloud Limited that allows this Application to incorporate the content of this kind on its pages. 

Personal Data collected: Usage data. 

Place of processing: Germany – [Privacy Policy](https://soundcloud.com/pages/privacy)

####  Spotify widget (Spotify AB) 

Spotify is an audio content delivery service provided by Spotify AB that allows this Application to incorporate the content of this kind on its pages. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. 

Place of processing: Sweden – [Privacy Policy](https://www.spotify.com/us/legal/privacy-policy/)

####  Vimeo video (Vimeo, LLC) 

Vimeo is a video content visualization service provided by Vimeo, LLC that allows this Application to incorporate the content of this kind on its pages. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://vimeo.com/privacy)

####  Vine widget (Vine Labs, Inc.) 

Vine is a video content visualization service provided by Vine Labs, Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate the content of this kind on its pages. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://vine.co/privacy)

####  YouTube video widget without cookies (Google Inc.) 

YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate the content of this kind on its pages.  
This widget is set up in a way that ensures that YouTube will not store information and cookies about Users on this Application unless they play the video. 

Personal Data collected: Usage data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

  * ###  Hosting and backend infrastructure 

This type of services has the purpose of hosting data and files that enable this Application to run and be distributed as well as to provide a ready-made infrastructure to run specific features or parts of this Application. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored. 

####  Amazon Web Services (Amazon) 

Amazon Web Services is a hosting service provided by Amazon.com Inc. 

Personal Data collected: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

  * ###  Infrastructure monitoring 

This kind of services allows this Application to monitor the use and behavior of its components so its performance, operation, maintenance and troubleshooting can be improved.  
Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and mode of implementation of these services, whose function is to filter the activities of this Application. 

####  New Relic (New Relic) 

New Relic is a monitoring service provided by New Relic Inc.  
The way New Relic is integrated means that it filters all traffic of this Application, i.e., communication between the Application and the User's browser or device, while also allowing analytical data on this Application to be collected. 

Personal Data collected: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://newrelic.com/privacy)

  * ###  Social features 

####  Public profile (This Application) 

Users may have public profiles that other Users can display. In addition to the Personal Data provided, this profile may contain Users' interactions with this Application. 

Personal Data collected: country, date of birth, gender, picture and username. 

  * ###  SPAM protection 

This type of services analyzes the traffic of this Application, potentially containing Users' Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM. 

####  Google reCAPTCHA (Google Inc.) 

Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc. 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. 

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/)

##  Further information about Personal Data 

  * ###  Selling goods and services online 

The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell products, including payment and possible delivery.  
The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by this Application depends on the payment system used. 

  * ###  The Service is not directed to minors under the age of 18 

Users declare themselves to be an adult according to their applicable legislation. Under no circumstance may persons under the age of 18 use this Application. 

##  Additional information about Data collection and processing 

###  Legal action 

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Data Controller may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities. 

###  Additional information about User's Personal Data 

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request. 

###  System logs and maintenance 

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address). 

###  Information not contained in this policy 

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document. 

###  The rights of Users 

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above. 

This Application does not support “Do Not Track” requests.  
To determine whether any of the third party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies. 

###  Changes to this privacy policy 

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request that the Data Controller remove the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users. 

###  Information about this privacy policy 

The Data Controller is responsible for this privacy policy, prepared starting from the modules provided by Iubenda and hosted on Iubenda's servers. 

###  Definitions and legal references 

####  Personal Data (or Data) 

Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number. 

####  Usage Data 

Information collected automatically from this Application (or third party services employed in this Application), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment. 

####  User 

The individual using this Application, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refers. 

####  Data Subject 

The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers. 

####  Data Processor (or Data Supervisor) 

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy. 

####  Data Controller (or Owner) 

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application. 

####  This Application 

The hardware or software tool by which the Personal Data of the User is collected. 

####  Cookies 

A small piece of data stored on the User's device. 

* * *

####  Legal information 

Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies. 

This privacy policy relates solely to this Application.
